35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing], circa 1971, circa 1970s; 17 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Decorated Christmas tree], 12
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Little boy sitting on "Santa's" lap], 13
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Two women standing behind a table, selling Christmas items], 14
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Inside of a church], 15
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Woman sitting in chair], 16
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Three little children sitting on "Santa's" lap], 17
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: People sitting inside of a church], 18
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Inside of a church], 19
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Inside of a church], 20
  - Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing], circa 1971, circa 1970s; 18 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Chapel], 1
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Chapel], 2
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Four people standing on a field], 3
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: People sitting in a church], 4
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Sign that reads "Christ Church on Quaker Hill"], 5
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Inside of Christ Church on Quaker Hill], 6
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Inside of Christ Church on Quaker Hill], 7
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Christ Church on Quaker Hill], 8
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Sign that reads "Christ Church on Quaker Hill"], 9
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Five people standing on a field, dressed nicely], 10
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: White sheet covering Thomas E. Dewey's commemorative plaque (?)], 11
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: White sheet covering Thomas E. Dewey's commemorative plaque (?)], 12
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Little boy pulling sheet off of Thomas E. Dewey's commemorative plaque, Lowell Thomas and pastor watching], 13
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Five people and Lowell Thomas on field next to a Thomas E. Dewey's commemorative plaque covered with a white sheet], 14
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Plaque that reads "These trees were planted as a living memorial to Thomas E. Dewey. Governor of the State of New York. 1943 - 1955 and his wife Frances Hutt Dewey"], 15
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Plaque that reads "These trees were planted as a living memorial to Thomas E. Dewey. Governor of the State of New York. 1943 - 1955 and his wife Frances Hutt Dewey"], 16
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Plaque that reads "These trees were planted as a living memorial to Thomas E. Dewey. Governor of the State of New York. 1943 - 1955 and his wife Frances Hutt Dewey." Lowell Thomas standing nearby], 17
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Plaque that reads "These trees were planted as a living memorial to Thomas E. Dewey. Governor of the State of New York. 1943 - 1955 and his wife Frances Hutt Dewey"], 18
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Plaque that reads "These trees were planted as a living memorial to Thomas E. Dewey. Governor of the State of New York. 1943 - 1955 and his wife Frances Hutt Dewey"], 19
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Plaque that reads "These trees were planted as a living memorial to Thomas E. Dewey. Governor of the State of New York. 1943 - 1955 and his wife Frances Hutt Dewey"], 20
  - Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing], circa 1971, circa 1970s; 19 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Bob in graduation cap and gown outside of Pawling High School], 1
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Bob in graduation cap and gown outside of Pawling High School with parents?], 2
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Bob in graduation cap and gown outside of Pawling High School with two other men], 3
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Christ Church on Quaker Hill], 4
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Bob in graduation cap and gown standing outside of Pawling High School], 5
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Lowell Thomas standing with pastor of Christ Church on Quaker Hill and little boy, beside plaque covered in white sheet], 6
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Bob in graduation cap and gown with another boy in graduation cap and gown, standing outside of Pawling High School], 7
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Boy in graduation cap and gown standing outside of Pawling High School with another man], 8
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Two boys in graduation cap and gown and man standing between them making a face; in front of Pawling High School], 9
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]:Bob and another boy in graduation caps and gowns, standing with three other people in front of Pawling High School], 10
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]:Bob and another boy in graduation caps and gowns, standing with three other people in front of Pawling High School], 11
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Boy in graduation cap and gown, standing in front of Pawling High School], 12
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Boy in graduation cap and gown, standing with a woman in front of Pawling High School], 13
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Bob and another boy in graduation caps and gowns standing in front of Pawling High School], 14
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Poinsettas on a table], 15
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Baby holding a sheet of paper], 16
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Bob in graduation cap and gown standing in front of Pawling High School], 17
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Little baby at a table, smiling], 18
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Baby and man on couch], 19
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Man sitting on chair], 20
  - Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing], circa 1971, circa 1970s; 20 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Baby walking], 1
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Man holding baby], 2
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Man playing piano, two other men and a woman watching], 3
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Baby standing at coffee table], 4
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Decorated Christmas tree], 5
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Man playing piano], 6
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Christmas tree and presents], 7
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Man and woman opening presents on Christmas], 8
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Presents underneath table with poinsettas], 9
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Presents underneath table with poinsettas], 10
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: People sitting on couches, Christmas time], 11
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Car parked in snow], 12
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: View from airplane], 13
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Airplane on snowy runway], 14
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Two men sitting on couch], 15
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Two men and a woman standing in a snowy parking lot], 16
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: View from airplane], 17
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Man putting baby into pajamas], 18
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Two men sitting at decorated dining table], 19
    - [Carousel number 8 [Christmas; unveiling of Thomas E. Dewey commemorative plaque at Christ Church on Quaker Hill (undated); Bob's graduation ceremony at Pawling High School (circa 1971); Alaska; skiing]: Lowell Thomas standing with four other people (relatives) in snowy parking lot], 20
  More
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1